A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, general correspondence, RG 2, 1952-1957 FA425
Rockefeller Archive Center
- General Correspondence, 1957
  - International, 1957; 1957/100
    - International - United Nations - W. H. O. - (A-P), 1957 (Box 9, Folder 74)
    - International - United Nations - W. H. O. - (Radiation), 1957 (Box 9, Folder 75)
    - International - United Nations - W. H. O. - (Radiation - Z), 1957 (Box 9, Folder 76)
    - International - Van Dyke - Vincent, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 77)
    - International - Watson, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 78)
    - International - Waugh, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 79)
    - International - Weaver, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 80)
    - International - (Webb - Whitman), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 81)
    - International - Work - Publications, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 82)
    - International - Work - Publications, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 83)
    - International - (World - Yudelman), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 84)
    - International - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/100.A
      - International - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - International - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/100.E
      - International - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - International - Malaria, 1957; 1957/100.I
      - International - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 85)
    - International - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/100.S
      - International - Diplomacy, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 86)
      - International - Diplomacy - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 87)
      - International - (F-Z), 1957 (Box 11, Folder 88)
  - United States, 1957; 1957/200
    - United States - (Aa - America), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 89)
    - United States - American - (A - Committee), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 90)
    - United States - American Council on Education, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 91)
    - United States - American Council on Education - (A - Education and International), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 92)
    - United States - American Council on Education - (Education of Women - Z), 1957 (Box 10, Folder 93)
    - United States - American - (Council for Emigres - E), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 94)
    - United States - American - (F), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 95)
    - United States - American - (G - Institute), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 96)
    - United States - American International Association - Indian Cooperatives, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 97)
    - United States - American - (Is - Library), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 98)
    - United States - American - (M), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 99)
    - United States - American - (N-O), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 100)
    - United States - American - (P), 1957 (Box 12, Folder 101)
    - United States - American Red Cross, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 102)
    - United States - American Red Cross - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - United States - American - (S-Z), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - United States - (Amerind-Asgrow), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 105)
    - United States - Asia Foundation - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 106)
    - United States - Asia Institute - Asia Society - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 107)
    - United States - (Ask - Associates), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 108)
    - United States - Association - (Aid - Am), 1957 (Box 13, Folder 109)
    - United States - Association - (Asian - Z), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 110)
    - United States - Atchley, D. W., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 111)
    - United States - (Atl - Aut), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 112)
    - United States - (Bab - Bay), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 113)
    - United States - (Baylor - Beth), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 114)
    - United States - (Bingham - Biosciences Information Exchange), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 115)
    - United States - Bird, R. D., 1957 (Box 14, Folder 116)
    - United States - (Bis - Boston), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - United States - (Bow - Bri), 1957 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - United States - (Broadcast - Brown, R.), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 119)
    - United States - (Brown University - California Export), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 120)
    - United States - California Institute of Technology - (A-Z) - (Calk - Carl), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 121)
    - United States - Carnegie Corporation - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 122)
    - United States - Carnegie Endowment - (A - International Relations Conference), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 123)
    - United States - Carnegie Endowment - International Relations Conference, Documents, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 124)
    - United States - Carnegie Endowment - (J-Z) - Carnegie Institute of Fine Arts, 1957 (Box 15, Folder 125)
    - United States - Carnegie Institute of Technology - (A-Z) - Carnegie Institute of Washington - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 126)
    - United States - (Carr - Chicago), 1957 (Box 15, Folder 127)
    - United States - (Chil - Clea), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 128)
    - United States - (Clem - College of Church), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 129)
    - United States - College of Medical Evangelists, 1957 (Box 16, Folder 130)
    - United States - (College of the Pacific - CBS), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 131)
    - United States - Columbia University - (A-C), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 132)
    - United States - Columbia University - (D - Ka), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 133)
    - United States - Columbia University - (Ke - Mar), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 134)
    - United States - Columbia University - (Mettler - Ryan), 1957 (Box 16, Folder 135)
    - United States - Columbia University - (Salmon - Wechsler), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 136)
    - United States - (Comet - Concert), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 137)
    - United States - (Conference - Connecticut), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 138)
    - United States - Conservation Foundation - Population Resources, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 139)
    - United States - (Contemporary - Cornell Medical Center/Z), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 140)
    - United States - Cornell University - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 141)
    - United States - (Corr - Council for Agricultural), 1957 (Box 17, Folder 142)
    - United States - Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 143)
    - United States - Council (F-Z), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 144)
    - United States - (Cow - Dan), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 145)
    - United States - (Dartmouth - Day), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 146)
    - United States - (Deale - Dexter), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 147)
    - United States - Duke University - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 148)
    - United States - (Dungan - Emory), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 149)
    - United States - (Encyclopedia - Faxon), 1957 (Box 18, Folder 150)
    - United States - (Fed - Flei), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 151)
    - United States - (Flet - Forbes), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 152)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (A-B), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 153)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (D-G), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 154)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (H - Nad), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 155)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - Near Eastern Studies, 1957 (Box 19, Folder 156)
    - United States - Ford Foundation - (Nie - Z), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 157)
    - United States - (Foreign - Fort), 1957 (Box 19, Folder 158)
    - United States - Foundation - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 159)
    - United States - Foundations - (January 1 - April 30, 1957) (Box 20, Folder 160)
    - United States - Foundations - (May 1 - December 31, 1957) (Box 20, Folder 161)
    - United States - (Fournier - Frye), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 162)
    - United States - Fulbright Program, 1957 (Box 20, Folder 163)
    - United States - Fulbright Program - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 164)
    - United States - Fuller, W. D. - Fund (A-Z), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 165)
    - United States - (Funk - General), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 166)
    - United States - (George - Glanville-Hicks), 1957 (Box 20, Folder 167)
    - United States - (Godsey - Gruse), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 168)
    - United States - (Guggenheim - Hartford), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 169)
    - United States - Harvard University - (A-I), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 170)
    - United States - Harvard University Law School - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 171)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Law - Schl), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 172)
    - United States - Harvard University School of Public Health, 1957 (Box 21, Folder 173)
    - United States - Harvard University - (Smith - Z), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 174)
    - United States - (Harvard-Yenching - Hayes), 1957 (Box 21, Folder 175)
    - United States - (Health - Hillside), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 176)
    - United States - (Hirsch - Hoxter), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 177)
    - United States - (Huffman - Hurley), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 178)
    - United States - (Illinois - Indiana), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 179)
    - United States - (Industrial - Industries), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 180)
    - United States - Institute - (A-E), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 181)
    - United States - Institute of International Education, 1957 (Box 22, Folder 182)
    - United States - Institute of International Education - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 183)
    - United States - Institute - (International Social - Z), 1957 (Box 22, Folder 184)
    - United States - (Inter-American - International Development), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 185)
    - United States - International Graphic Arts Society, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 186)
    - United States - (International Hall - Izenour, G. C.), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 187)
    - United States - (Jack, H. A. - John Price Jones), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 188)
    - United States - Johns Hopkins University - (A-K), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 189)
    - United States - Johns Hopkins University - (L-Z), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 190)
    - United States - (Johnson - Juniata), 1957 (Box 23, Folder 191)
    - United States - Kansas City Art Institute, 1957 (Box 23, Folder 192)
    - United States - (K), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 193)
    - United States - (Ladies - Lazaron), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 194)
    - United States - Laymen's Movement for a Christian World, Inc., 1957 (Box 24, Folder 195)
    - United States - (Lea - Liberty), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 196)
    - United States - Library of Congress - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 197)
    - United States - (Library - Luhrman), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 198)
    - United States - (Mc), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 199)
    - United States - (Malone - Massachusetts Higher), 1957 (Box 24, Folder 200)
    - United States - MIT - (A-H), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 201)
    - United States - MIT - (K-Z), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 202)
    - United States - (Master - Meharry), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 203)
    - United States - (Mellon - Metropolitan Opera), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 204)
    - United States - Michigan State University - (A-G), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 205)
    - United States - Michigan State University - (H-Z), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 206)
    - United States - (Microcard - Miller, B.), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 207)
    - United States - (Miller, C. J. - Mitchell, E.), 1957 (Box 25, Folder 208)
    - United States - (Modern - Museum of Modern Art), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 209)
    - United States - (Museum of Navajo - My), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 210)
    - United States - (Nag - National Association), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 211)
    - United States - National - (Board - Broadcasting), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 212)
    - United States - National - (Can - Cath), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 213)
    - United States - National - (Comm - Council), 1957 (Box 26, Folder 214)
    - United States - National - (Ed - Info), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 215)
    - United States - National Institute of Health - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 216)
    - United States - National - (Institute of Mental - Lib), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 217)
    - United States - National - (Op - Res), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 218)
    - United States - National Science Foundation - (A - Ba), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 219)
    - United States - National Science Foundation - (Br - Z), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 220)
    - United States - (National Society - News), 1957 (Box 27, Folder 221)
    - United States - New York - (A-C), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 222)
    - United States - New York - (H-T), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 223)
    - United States - New York University - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 224)
    - United States - (New York Zoological - Nu), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 225)
    - United States - (Oak - Ohio River), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 226)
    - United States - Ohio State University - (L-Z), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 227)
      General note
      There was no folder for Ohio State University (La-M).
    - United States - (Ohio University - Pal), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 228)
    - United States - Pan American - (B - Sanitary Bureau), 1957 (Box 28, Folder 229)
    - United States - Pan American Sanitary Bureau - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 230)
    - United States - Pan American Union - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 231)
    - United States - (Pan American Trade - Per), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 232)
    - United States - People to People Program, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 233)
    - United States - People to People Program, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 234)
    - United States - People to People Program - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 235)
    - United States - (Pfizer - Princeton Theological), 1957 (Box 29, Folder 236)
    - United States - Princeton University - (A-Pop), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 237)
    - United States - Princeton University - (Pre - Z), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 238)
    - United States - (Prit - Q), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 239)
    - United States - (Rad - Rand), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 240)
    - United States - (Randolph - Rep), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 241)
    - United States - (Res - Rob), 1957 (Box 30, Folder 242)
    - United States - Rockefeller - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 243)
    - United States - (Rockford - Russo), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 244)
    - United States - (Rust - Rutter), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 245)
    - United States - (Sacks - Saphier), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 246)
    - United States - (Sarah - Sell), 1957 (Box 31, Folder 247)
    - United States - (Sha - Sister), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 248)
    - United States - Slavic Studies Joint Committee - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 249)
    - United States - (Sle - Sol), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 250)
    - United States - (Southeastern - Southwestern), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 251)
    - United States - (Spa - Sta), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 252)
    - United States - Stanford - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 253)
    - United States - (Star - Stu), 1957 (Box 32, Folder 254)
    - United States - (Sun - Thi), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 255)
    - United States - (Tho - Tufts), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 256)
    - United States - (Tul - Twe), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 257)
    - United States - (Union - United Negro), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 258)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - (A-F), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 259)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - (G-I), 1957 (Box 33, Folder 260)
    - United States - United States - Agriculture - (J-Z), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 261)
    - United States - United States - (Air - B), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 262)
    - United States - United States - (C-E), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 263)
    - United States - United States - (F - Imm), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 264)
    - United States - United States Information Agency - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 265)
    - United States - United States - Interior/Z - ICA/H, 1957 (Box 34, Folder 266)
    - United States - United States - ICA - (I-Z), 1957 (Box 34, Folder 267)
    - United States - United States - (L - Sen), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 268)
    - United States - United States - State - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 269)
    - United States - United States/Z - University/Ari, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 270)
    - United States - University - (Ark - Buf), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 271)
    - United States - University of California - (A-F), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 272)
    - United States - University of California - (G-L), 1957 (Box 35, Folder 273)
    - United States - University of California - (M-Z), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 274)
    - United States - University - (Cha/Z - Chi/P), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 275)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (Q - Social), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 276)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (South Asian Studies), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 0276A)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (South Asian Studies), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 0276B)
    - United States - University of Chicago - (Ste - Z), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 0276C)
    - United States - University - (Cin - Det), 1957 (Box 36, Folder 277)
    - United States - University of Florida - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 278)
    - United States - University - (Geo - Ken), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 279)
    - United States - University - (Lou - Mia), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 280)
    - United States - University of Michigan - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 281)
    - United States - University - (Micr - Min), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 282)
    - United States - University - (Mis - New), 1957 (Box 37, Folder 283)
    - United States - University of North Carolina - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 284)
    - United States - University - (Not - Ore), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 285)
    - United States - University of Pennsylvania - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 286)
    - United States - University - (Pit - South), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 287)
    - United States - University of Southern California - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 288)
    - United States - University - (Ten - Vir), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 289)
    - United States - University of Washington - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 38, Folder 290)
    - United States - University - (Wis - Wyo), 1957 (Box 39, Folder 291)
    - United States - (Ut - Ven), 1957 (Box 39, Folder 292)
    - United States - (Ver - vonVorys), 1957 (Box 39, Folder 293)
    - United States - (Wab - Wesl), 1957 (Box 39, Folder 294)
    - United States - (West - Wins), 1957 (Box 39, Folder 295)
    - United States - (Wint - Wright Oral), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 296)
    - United States - (Wright, R. - Yale/E), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 297)
    - United States - Yale University - (Far - Mue), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 298)
    - United States - Yale/Z - Z, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 299)
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/200.A
      - United States - (Bay - Johns), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 300)
      - United States - Medical Education, 1957 (Box 40, Folder 301)
      - United States - (New - Tul), 1957 (Box 40, Folder 302)
      - United States - University - (Ark - Min), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 303)
      - United States - University of North Carolina - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 304)
      - United States - University of North Carolina - (Medical School) - A Compendium of Reports, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 0304A)
      - United States - University of North Carolina - (Medical School) - A Compendium of Reports, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 0304B)
      - United States - University of North Carolina - (Medical School) - A Compendium of Reports, 1957 (Box 41, Folder 0304C)
      - United States - University - (Pen - Was), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 305)
      - United States - University of Wisconsin - (Medical School), 1957 (Box 41, Folder 306)
      - United States - (Was - Wes), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 307)
      - United States - (Yal - Yes), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 308)
    - United States - Nursing, 1957; 1957/200.C
      - United States - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 309)
    - United States - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/200.D
      - United States - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 310)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/200.E
      - United States - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 310)
    - United States - Declinations, 1957; 1957/200.F
      - United States - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 310)
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/200.R
      - United States - (A-R), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 311)
      - United States - (S-Z), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 312)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/200.S
      - United States - (A-R), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 313)
      - United States - SSRC - (A-K), 1957 (Box 42, Folder 314)
      - United States - SSRC - (Legal), 1957 (Box 43, Folder 315)
      - United States - SSRC - (M-Nat), 1957 (Box 43, Folder 316)
      - United States - SSRC - (Near Eastern Studies), 1957 (Box 43, Folder 317)
      - United States - SSRC - (Near Eastern Studies) - Dobbs Ferry Conference, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 318)
      - United States - SSRC - (Near Eastern Studies) - Dobbs Ferry Conference, 1957 (Box 43, Folder 319)
      - United States - (SSRC/Z-University/M), 1957 (Box 43, Folder 320)
      - United States - (University/N-Z), 1957 (Box 43, Folder 321)
  - Alaska, 1957; 1957/202
    - Alaska, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - California, 1957; 1957/205
    - California, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - Panama Canal Zone, 1957; 1957/206
    - Panama Canal Zone, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - Hawaii, 1957; 1957/214
    - Hawaii, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - Maryland, 1957; 1957/223
    - Maryland, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - New York, 1957; 1957/235
    - New York, 1957 (Box 44, Folder 322)
  - Philippines, 1957; 1957/242
    - Philippine Republic - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 323)
    - Philippine Republic - University of the Philippines - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 324)
    - Philippines - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/242.E
      - Philippine Republic - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 325)
    - Philippines - Declinations, 1957; 1957/242.F
      - Philippine Republic - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 325)
    - Philippines - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/242.R
      - Philippine Republic - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 325)
  - Puerto Rico, 1957; 1957/243
    - Puerto Rico - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 326)
    - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 44, Folder 327)
    - Puerto Rico - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/243.A
      - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico - (Medical School), 1957 (Box 45, Folder 328)
      - Puerto Rico - University of Puerto Rico - Medical School - (January-December), 1957 (Box 45, Folder 329)
    - Puerto Rico - Nursing, 1957; 1957/243.C
      - Puerto Rico, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 330)
    - Puerto Rico - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/243.S
      - Puerto Rico, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 330)
  - Pacific Islands, 1957; 1957/258
    - Pacific Islands Trust Territory, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 330)
  - South America, 1957; 1957/300
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (January-June), 1957 (Box 45, Folder 331)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (July-December), 1957 (Box 45, Folder 332)
    - South America and Latin America - Administration - (Exchange of Personnel), 1957 (Box 45, Folder 333)
    - South America and Latin America - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 334)
    - South America and Latin America - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences - (A-Z) - Pan American, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 335)
    - South America - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/300.A
      - South America and Latin America - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 336)
    - South America - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/300.E
      - South America and Latin America - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 336)
    - South America - Social Sciences, 1957; 1957/300.S
      - South America and Latin America - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 336)
  - Argentina, 1957; 1957/301
    - Argentina - (A-T), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 336)
    - Argentina - (U-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 337)
    - Argentina - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/301.A
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 338)
    - Argentina - Natural Sciences and Agriculture, 1957; 1957/301.D
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 338)
    - Argentina - Humanities and Arts, 1957; 1957/301.R
      - Argentina - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 338)
  - Bolivia, 1957; 1957/303
    - Bolivia - Medical Sciences, 1957; 1957/303.A
      - Bolivia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 338)
    - Bolivia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 1957; 1957/303.E
      - Bolivia - (A-Z), 1957 (Box 46, Folder 338)
  - Brazil, 1957; 1957/305